We have to walk again?
(水月)
また歩くのか… もうヘトヘトだよ。
I'm exhausted.
Humph... We're going to
the northern hideout now.
(香燐)ヘッ… これから
北アジトに行くっていうのに➡
At this rate, you'll be killed
the moment we get there.
そんなんじゃ
着いたとたんに殺されちまうぞ。
I only know it through maps...
but is the place really that bad?
(水月)
ボクは地図でしか知らないけど➡
そんなに やばいとこなんだ？
北アジトは ただのアジトじゃない。
The northern hideout
is no ordinary hideout.
That place...
あそこは 人体実験場だ。
is where human experiments
are conducted.
そして そこで生み出された➡
And the unmanageable monsters that
result are kept locked up there.
手のつけられないバケモノばかりが
収容されてる。
A male...
(重吾)男… いや… やっぱり女…。
No, a female.
次に殺すのは やっぱり男だ。
No, I'll kill a male next, after all.
(重吾)
そうか… もう始めやがったか。
I see.
It's already begun...
Why... Why did you have to die?
どうして… どうしてお前は
死んじまったんだよ。
(ナルト)ふぁ～い。
That's pretty heavy food
to have in the morning.
RAMEN
(サクラ)寝起きから
ヘビーなもん食ってんな アンタ…。
Sakura-chan, today's our day off.
How come you're up so early?
サクラちゃん
今日は休日だってばよ。
こんな朝早くから何？
It's already noon.
もう お昼だよ。
Well, never mind.
まぁ いいや。
Just wash up quickly and get dressed.
I'll be waiting.
すぐに顔洗って着替えてきて。
待ってるから。
なに!? デート？
Huh? Is it a date?
Idiot! Tsunade-sama has summoned us!
バカ！ 綱手様が呼んでんのよ！
Say, aren't you tired?
ねぇ 疲れただろ？
少し休憩にしないか？
How about a short break?
You're already taking a break!
つ～か
もう休んでんじゃねえか！
You are so hopeless!
ったく だらしないヤツだな。
北アジトまで まだまだだぞ。
We've still got a ways to go 'til
we get to the northern hideout!
My destination is different
from yours.
キミとは行き先が違うんだ。
No need to bother with me.
Just go on ahead.
ボクの心配は結構。 もう行ってくれ。
I remembered that I too have business
at the northern hideout!
ウチも北アジトに
用があるのを思い出した！
So I'm going to take care of that first!
そっちを
先に行くことにしたんだよ！
チッ！
((重吾 : うおぉ～っ！
Move...!
どけ～っ！ 殺すぞ テメエも！
I'll kill you too!
Stop it, Jugo...
(君麻呂)やめろ 重吾。
That's...
もう… いい。
enough.
You're not alone.
お前は１人じゃない。
(ボクがついてる))
You have me.
Without you...
お前がいないんじゃ➡
I can never leave this place...
オレはもう
一生ここからは出られない。
Suigetsu...
水月…
なんでアンタは サスケについてくる？
Why do you follow Sasuke?
I have a goal.
ボクには目的がある。
サスケといると それが叶うからさ。
And if I stick with Sasuke,
I can fulfill that goal.
Say, I should be asking you
the same question... Really.
ていうか そりゃ
こっちのセリフだよね～ ホント。
アンタたちの
目的が何かは知らないけど➡
I don't know what your goals are...
But you want me to join your team
despite knowing about Jugo?
重吾のことを知ってて
仲間にするって言ってんのか？
I know him a little.
We fought each other once.
少しはね…。 一度
手合わせさせられたこともあるよ。
He had an unusual ability
and was quite formidable.
おもしろい能力を使うヤツで
かなり強かったけど…。
But I couldn't figure out
what he was thinking,
何考えてるかわからない感じで
好きにはなれなかったけどね。
and I didn't really like him.
I understand he  sought out
Orochimaru.
自分から
大蛇丸に捕まりに来たらしいし➡
He's got to be crazy.
頭が どうかしてる。
According to rumors,
ウワサじゃ重吾は➡
Jugo usually has that
unusual impulse well under control.
ふだん その異常な衝動を
抑え込んでるらしいけど➡
But when he loses it,
he transforms into a ruthless killer.
キレたら恐るべき殺人鬼へと
性格も見た目も変貌するって話だ。
His personality and appearance
change completely.
へぇ～。 要は人殺しが大好きな
イカレ野郎ってことだろう？
In other words, he's a maniac
who loves to kill people.
But to Orochimaru,
Jugo's ability was enticing.
それでも 大蛇丸にとって
重吾の能力は魅力的だった。
He invented an enzyme,
based on Jugo's body fluids,
大蛇丸は重吾の体液から➡
which induced the same condition
in other Shinobi.
他の忍にも同じ状態を引き起こす
酵素を開発したんだからね。
You guys know it too, right?
アンタたちも知ってるだろう？
That's... the Curse Mark.
それが… 呪印だよ。
Jugo is the one and only
original carrier.
重吾は その唯一のオリジナルだ。
I'm getting out of here!
I'll kill anyone who tries to stop me!
オレは ここから出る！
ジャマをするヤツは殺す！
Who's... next?
次は どいつだ!?
sha la la some day in the future
sha la la itsuka kitto
I will for sure hold it in my hand
boku wa te ni suru nda
it will softly set ablaze
hakanaki mune ni sotto
a light in my empty heart
hikari moeteyuke
the "impulses" that makes you want to meet it
aitaku naru no shoudou
the "innocence" that makes you want to cry
nakitaku naru no junjou
they've gone into the summer fire
natsu no hi ni tobikonda
the fireflies aren't coming back
hotaru wa kaeranai
you didn't say a single word and left a kiss for me behind
anata wa nanimo iwazu kuchizuke wo nokoshite
and nodded as you still got burned
kitsuzuku mama unazuita ne
it was so sad that my life was wavering
kanashii hodo inochi yurameiteita
sha la la some day in the future
sha la la itsuka kitto
I will for sure hold it in my hand
boku wa te ni suru nda
it will softly set ablaze
hakanaki mune ni sotto
a light in my empty heart
hikari moeteyuke
sha la la my sweet lovely dear
sha la la itoshiki hito
I can also see you right now
anata mo mieteiru no
the dazzling moon will softly
mabayui tsuki ga sotto
illuminate the morning day
ashita wo terashite
and strongly and strongly shine on
tsuyoku tsuyoku kagayaite
Jugo of the
Northern Hideout
(綱手)遅い！
何をチンタラしてた!? ったく！
You're late!
What took you two so long?! Cripes!
す… すみません！
I-I'm sorry.
Naruto was eating lunch,
which he calls breakfast...
ナルトのヤツが朝食という名の
お昼を食べてまして…。
Now now... Tsunade...
(自来也)まぁまぁ 綱手。
Huh? Pervy Sage?! You're back!
あれ？
エロ仙人 帰ってきてたのかよ。
久しぶりだのぉ ナルト！
It's been awhile, eh, Naruto?
Aw man! Why didn't you tell me
you were back?
なんだよ！ 帰ってきてたんなら
教えてくれりゃあ…。
We had a hard time after you left.
あれから大変だったんだぞ。
(自来也)そうらしいのぉ。
So I hear.
大方の話は聞いておるが
大活躍だったようだのぉ。
I got the gist of it, but I understand
you played a big part.
That's for sure.
あぁ そうなんだ。
オレってば ついに➡
I finally got my Collaboration Jutsu
to work in sync with the two toads.
ガマたちとのコラボ忍術を
完成させたぜ！
Oh, is that so?! You finally did it!
おぉ そうか そうか！
ついにやったか！
How about it?
Wanna see my new Jutsu?
どうだ？ 新術 見てえだろ？
おぉ せっかくだし。
Well, since I'm here...
I don't mind if I do.
見てみたいのぉ。
だろ？ だろ？
I knew it!
And naturally, after that,
we'll go eat ramen at Ichiraku!
で そのあとはもちろん 一楽で
ミソチャーシューで決まりだってばよぉ。
おぉ おごってやるとも！
お～！ 行こうぜ行こうぜ！
Sure, it'll be my treat.
- All right! Let's get going!
- Let's go! Your new Jutsu, eh...?
よ～し 行こう行こう。
新術かぁ 楽しみだ。
- I'm looking forward to this...
- Hey!!
(綱手/サクラ)ごらぁ！
- Ow!
- Oh!
だぁ～！
(自来也)お～。
ねぇ… 少し休まない？
Say, can we rest a bit?
水月 テメエ休んでばっかじゃねえか。
もうアジトだぞ！
Suigetsu! You keep stopping to rest!
We're almost at the hideout!
その刀か！ その刀が重いのか!?
Is it the sword?
Is it too heavy for you?
Then leave it, damn it!
それ 置いてけこら～！
サスケも なんとか言えよ！ ん？
Tell him, Sasuke!
どうした？
What's wrong?
(サスケ)見張り小屋のヤツは どこだ？
え？
Where's the guy who's on watch?
Huh?
あ… ホントだ おかしいね。
You're right... That's strange.
おい。
Hey...
北アジトの男だ。 まだ息がある。
He's from the northern hideout.
He's still breathing.
何があった？
What happened?
お… お前は うちはサスケか…。
Y-You're... Uchiha Sasuke...
助けてくれ…。
Help me...
What happened?
どうしたんだ？
I-It all started...
大蛇丸が
死んだという情報から始まった。
with the rumors that
Orochimaru was dead.
囚人たちが暴れだし➡
The prisoners went wild...
At this rate...
このままじゃ… うっ！
Oh dear... He died.
あららら 死んじゃった。
お前は たしか…。
You're...
What is that?
なんなの あれ。
He's already in the
"Curse Mark Second State".
呪印状態２だ。
すでに変化してやがる。
The northern hideout is over there.
北アジトは そこだ。
さっさと重吾に会いにいくぞ。
Let's go and see Jugo.
Huh? Hey! Wait, Sasuke!
あ… おい！ 待て サスケ！
Huh? Who is this guy?
あれ？ 誰なの？ これ。
男…。
次に殺すのは やっぱり男だ。
A male...
The next one I kill
will be a guy, after all...
All right, decided.
よし 決めた。
If the next one who comes
through that door is a woman,
次に その扉から入ってきたヤツが
女だったら➡
殺すことにしよう。
I'll kill her.
The guards have all been killed...
看守は全滅だな。
全員 脱獄しちまってる。
and the prisoners have escaped.
Then there's no way
we can tell which one is Jugo...
あれじゃ どれが重吾か
わかんないね… サスケ。
Eh, Sasuke?
Karin, is Jugo among them?
香燐 アイツらの中に重吾はいるか？
Cripes, what a pain!
Just wait a bit!
ったく うるさいな！
少し待ってろ！
Nope, he's not.
(香燐)フン… いないな。
Well then, I can fight without
worrying who they are.
(水月)なら おかまいなしってヤツで
オーケーだね。
急所は はずしておけ。
Just avoid killing them.
ハァ～ やっぱキミは
木ノ葉出身だなぁ。
You're from the Hidden Leaf,
after all...
You should've killed that
guy back there too, you know.
さっきの男も
殺せばよかったのに。
So naïve...
甘いね。
いくぞ。
Let's go.
うわっ！
うぉ～っ！
Stay away! You all stink!
寄るな！ 汗くせえ！
つええ… お前は…。
You're strong... You're...
フゥ～。
鍵だ。 見つけたぞ。
The keys!
I found them!
(重吾)殺す… 殺す！
Kill...
香燐 どっちだ？ 案内しろ。
Karin, which way?
Lead the way.
Sasuke!
Why're you ordering me around, huh?!
サスケ アンタ さっきから
なに仕切ってんだ！
Can you just hurry and check?
いいから
早く調べてくれないかな。
それがキミ ご自慢の能力だろ。
That's the ability you
pride yourself on, right?
あっちだ。
That way!
フゥ～…。
なんだ？
What is it?
Actually, it's this way.
ホントは こっちだ。
Let's go, Sasuke!
さぁ 行くぞ サスケ。
Why did you lie? Suigetsu went...
なぜ ウソをつく？
水月は あっちに…。
Suigetsu has a big mouth,
that's why I don't like him.
うるさいから 水月は嫌いだ。
行くぞ！
離せ 自分で歩く。
Let's go!
Let go... I can walk on my own.
しかし 呪印ってのは➡
So... the Curse Mark really does transform
the body into such an ugly shape...
体型を あそこまで
ブサイクに変化させるんだね。
Sasuke, does your Curse Mark
do the same to you?
サスケ キミも 呪印で
あんなふうになるのかい？
Sasuke... Are you listening...?
サスケ？ ボクの話をちゃんと…。
That witch...!
あの女…！
A woman...
女だ… 女が入ってきたら… 殺す。
If a woman enters,
I'll kill her...!
Here?
ここか。
あぁ 重吾は 中にいる。
Yeah, Jugo's inside.
There...
来たな。
Now then, which will it be?
さあ どっちだ？
よし。 じゃあ開けるぞ。
All right! I'm gonna open it!
I'll go in first. Karin, stay back.
オレが先に入る。
香燐 お前は下がってろ。
S-Sure!
お おう。
No...
いや…。
It's gotta be a guy.
If it's a guy, I'll kill him.
やっぱり男だ。
男が入ってきたら殺そう。
Bingo! I'm gonna kill!
ビンゴ！ 殺す！
He's coming!
来た！
おらぁ～！
Huh? I'm back where I started.
あれ？ 戻ってきちゃったな。
I should've turned right back there.
やっぱり あそこを右か。
Damn that witch!
クソッ あの女。
Y-You guys...
お前ら…。
Just what is your purpose
in coming here?
お前らはいったい
何が目的でここへ来た？
We came to take Jugo outta here,
so that he can join our team.
重吾を連れ出しにきただけだけど。
仲間にしたくてね。
Do you guys realize...
what you're doing?
お前ら 自分たちが
なにをしようとしてんのか➡
わかってんのか？
If you let that guy...
out into the world...
あんなヤツを この世に放したら…。
I totally agree.
ボクも同感。
けど ボクが言い聞かせるさ。
But I'll convince him...
with force, if necessary.
なんなら力ずくでね。
強いといっても アンタ程度じゃ…。
You may be strong, but you're hardly...
Listen... If it weren't for Sasuke's words,
you'd be dead right now.
キミ サスケの言葉がなけりゃ
今 死んでたとこだよ。
テメエらなんか 重吾に殺されちまえ。
Jugo will kill you all!
I really could care less
if one person died.
一人くらい かまいやしないか。
Sasuke!
サスケ！
ゲハハッ！
アハハッ。 ハァ。
I-I'm so sorry!
Naruto always gets so rowdy...
すみません。 ナルトのヤツが
毎度まいど騒がしくって。
Hey, Naruto, you idiot!
Say you're sorry too!!
こら バカナルト！
イテッ！
アンタも謝んなさいよ。
Oww... Sakura-chan that hurt!
サクラちゃん 痛いってばよ。
And? What did you want
to talk about?
で なんなんですか 話って？
Huh? Mmm...
ん？ うむ…。
What's wrong, Grandma Tsunade?
どうしたんだよ
綱手のばあちゃん。
Don't you have something
to talk about?
なんか話があるんじゃねえの？
そうだな。
Well...
There's certain information that is
being spread throughout the region...
実は 各地いたるところで
ある情報が流れていてな。
It's about that.
そのことについてだ。
情報？
Information?
What? What about?
なに？ なんだってばよ？
Orochimaru is dead.
大蛇丸が死んだ。
どうやら
うちはサスケがやったらしい。
It seems Uchiha Sasuke killed him.
Is...
そ… それって… ホントか!?
Is that... true?
There's no mistake about it.
I heard it from a reliable source.
まず間違いない…。
確かな情報スジから
聞いたからのぉ…。
Then...
じゃあ もう…。
アハッハッハ！ アイツが大蛇丸なんかに
やられるはずがねえってばよ！
Heh! After all, there's no way
he'd get killed by Orochimaru!
That means Sasuke will be coming back
to the Hidden Leaf! Right?
じゃあ サスケのヤツ
木ノ葉に帰ってくんだよな！
なぁ!?
That doesn't seem to be the case...
どうやら そうではないらしい…。
えっ…。
ゲハハハハ！
クッ…。
It's not over yet!
まだだ！
クッ！
Sasuke's Chakra...
《サスケのチャクラが…》
...changed!
変化した…。
ゲハハハ… また オレのコピー野郎か!?
Not another copy of me...!
ハッハッハッハ！
Sasuke...
《サスケ…》
But you're quite a guy
しかし 部分変化ができるとは
たいした野郎だぜ！
to be able to do
a Partial Transformation!
You're good at controlling
your Curse Mark!
呪印を扱うのが うめえな！
I have no intention of fighting.
争う気はない。
I only wish to talk to you, Jugo.
お前に話があるだけだ 重吾。
keep your pants and shirt on even if you're unable to do it right now
ima dekinakute mo aseranaide awatenaide
you should believe in yourself and take it at your own pace
kimi no mai peesu de jibun shinjite yukkuri ikeba ii
life always throws you curveballs and the reason of that is
yo kono yo wa hitosujinawa de ikanai sore wa naze nara
it's a test made by God so that's why it's quite hard
kamisama ga tsukutta tesuto dakara muzukashii nda
arts? science? or rather how about ethics?
bunkei rikei mushiro doutoku kimi nara kore wo dou toku
this is just like life so put your heart and soul into seriousness
kore wa maru de jinsei dakara uchikomu shinken ni
we worry ourselves lose ourselves and we keep asking ourselves questions
bokura wa nayamu mayou nandomo jibun ni toikakeru
we aren't one and relentesly persue our search for answers
hitotsu ja nai kotae sagashi gamushara ni oikakeru
keep your pants and shirt on even if you're unable to do it right now
ima dekinakute mo aseranaide awatenaide
you should believe in yourself and take it at your own pace
kimi no mai peesu de jibun shinjite yukkuri ikeba ii
the current me would tell me that if I was from the future
mirai no bokura nara ima no boku ni oshiete agerareru
you should keep pursuing it until your efforts change yourself
kimi no doryoku ga jishin ni kawaru toki made oitsuzukereba ii
Next Episode
But you're quite a guy!
ヘヘ… ヤマト隊長からもらった福引券。
You're good at controlling
your Curse Mark!
狙うは もちろん１等！
カップラーメン １年分だ！
I have no intention of fighting.
I only wish to talk to you.
おっ ここだ！
(いの)いらっしゃ…
って なんだ ナルトか。
Talk?
Jugo, I'm getting you out of here.
なんだじゃねえだろ！
ところで オレのカップメン まだある？
Are you an idiot?!
You don't know anything!
オレのかどうかは 運次第ね。
けど まだ出てないわよ １等！
What do you mean?
He's gone. That's why...
よっしゃ～！
はい じゃあ３回ね。
I can never leave this place!
頼むぞ ラーメン！
Next time: "Formation!"
Formation!
(いの)残念！
はい ハズレのアメちゃん。
Captain Yamato gave me
some raffle tickets!
クッソ～ 次こそ！
(いの)ハズレ！
はい アメちゃん パート２！
Naturally, I'm going for first prize...
A year's supply of Cup Noodles!!
最後の１回に すべてをかける！
おらぁ～!!
Huh? This must be it.
"RAFFLE TICKET BOOTH"
Welcome...!
Oh, it's just you, Naruto.
(２人)あ！
大当たり～！
Don't give me that attitude!
By the way,
are my cup noodles still here?
やった～！
はい！
Whether it's yours or not
depends on your luck.
特賞の自来也先生サイン入り➡
『イチャイチャタクティクス』３冊セット！
But, no first-prize winners yet!
"FIRST PRIZE"
All right!!
え～!? そんなのいるか！
Okay. You get three tries.
アホらしい 帰ろ 帰ろ。
Come on ramen!
Sorry! Here's a candy for
drawing a blank.
(カカシ)あれ？ 特賞出ちゃったの？
せっかく
福引券集めたのに… ショック。
Damn it! Next one for sure!
You lose! Here's your second candy.
I'm putting everything
on this last try!
(ナツ)『FAIRY TAIL』 前回までは…。
(ハッピー)ついに始まった➡
- Oh!
Jack pot!!
Ｓ級魔導士昇格試験！
Yay!
- Here.
- Huh?!
第１次試験は
バトルもあるルートを選んで➡
The grand prize signed by Jiraiya-sensei himself.
勝ち進まなくちゃ
いけないんだけど➡
The entire Make-Out Tactics Book Set!
ナツの相手は いきなりギルダーツ！
What?! Who needs this?!
まぁ 苦戦したけど
手加減してやったからなぁ。
This is stupid! I'm going home!
(ハッピー)すごい強がり…。
Huh? They already won the grand prize?
"GRAND PRIZE"
And here I got these raffle tickets...
How depressing!